<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About Me</string>
    <string name="name">Saumil Patel</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow Star</string>
    <string name="bio">"A motivated and enthusiastic graduate with a Masters in Information Technology seeking a position to utilize my skills, particularly in the area of Android development. Happiest when tackling diverse challenges, naturally inquisitive and problem solver. Highly adaptable to challenging environments, having strong work ethics and commitment to professional development. Currently, looking for a suitable position where I can use my existing skills in Android development and grow in my career. Strong communication skills, both written and verbal, developed while completing my Master’s degree and liaising with clients and colleagues at Police Tax and in other part-time work roles. Strong listening skills and ability to make informed decisions in high pressure situations. Strong team spirit and ability to lead and work autonomously when required.  Participated in weekly meetings and was part of a values team at Urban Maintenance Systems. An ability to think creatively and technically and turn concepts into reality – designed and created 3 Apps for as part of academic and industrial internship training. A motivated and enthusiastic graduate with a Masters in Information Technology seeking a position to utilize my skills, particularly in the area of Android development. Happiest when tackling diverse challenges, naturally inquisitive and problem solver. Highly adaptable to challenging environments, having strong work ethics and commitment to professional development. Currently, looking for a suitable position where I can use my existing skills in Android development and grow in my career. Strong communication skills, both written and verbal, developed while completing my Master’s degree and liaising with clients and colleagues at Police Tax and in other part-time work roles. Strong listening skills and ability to make informed decisions in high pressure situations. Strong team spirit and ability to lead and work autonomously when required.  Participated in weekly meetings and was part of a values team at Urban Maintenance Systems. An ability to think creatively and technically and turn concepts into reality – designed and created 3 Apps for as part of academic and industrial internship training."</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_nick_name">What is your nick name?</string>
</resources>
